Finding Aid for Episcopal Church, Diocese of Western Michigan records, 1851-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Diocesan Historiographer
  - Betty Sutton
    - Clergy, biographical and related materials
      - Bradley, Clement Grenelle (Box 105)
      - Brana, Wayne Michael (Box 105)
      - Brehe, Stephen Louis (Box 105)
      - Brewin, George M. (Box 105)
      - Brinkmoller, Leonard (Box 105)
      - Brittain, William (Box 105)
      - Brookins, Charles Frederick (Box 105)
      - Brown, Belno Addison (Box 105)
      - Brown, Daniel E. (Box 105)
      - Brown, James A. (Box 105)
      - Brown, Kenneth Evans (Box 105)
      - Brown, Leo Maxwell (Box 105)
      - Brown, Lewis R. (Box 105)
      - Bruce, Caleb A. (Box 105)
      - Bruce, Henry (Box 105)
      - Brumbaugh, George William (Box 105)
      - Bryce, David George (Box 105)
      - Buck, Minerson Erastus (Box 105)
      - Buel, Samuel (Box 105)
      - Bunday, Roger Jack (Box 105)
      - Burch, Charles Sumner (Box 105)
      - Burford, Spruille R. (Box 105)
      - Burger, David R. (Box 105)
      - Burgess, A. Mead (Box 105)
      - Burr, Dudley Holcomb (Box 105)
      - Burton, William (Box 105)
      - Bush, Augustus (Box 105)
      - Bush, Harvey Safford (Box 105)
      - Bustrin, Robert Craig (Box 105)
      - Butler, Pierce (Box 105)
      - Butler, Vincent (Box 105)
      - Cairns, Alexander Augustus (Box 105)
      - Callahan, Gary Edward (Box 105)
      - Campbell, Edward Joseph, Jr. (Box 105)
      - Carey, Donald Von (Box 105)
      - Carlton, John Gowan (Box 105)
      - Carrington, Francis L. (Box 105)
      - Carter, Philander Lothrop, III (Box 105)
      - Carter, William Irwin (Box 105)
      - Carty, Adolphus (Box 105)
      - Cell, John Albert (Box 105)
      - Chambers, Henry D. (Box 105)
      - Chambers, James Taylor (Box 105)
      - Chapin, Densmore D. (Box 105)
      - Chapin, Seth Smith (Box 105)
      - Charles, C. W. (Box 105)
      - Charles, William (Box 105)
      - Chase, Philander (Box 105)
      - Chase, Samuel (Box 105)
      - Chidester, Keith (Box 105)
      - Childs, Robert Sawyer (Box 105)
      - Choquette, Henry Holmes (Box 105)
      - Christian, Ellis Alvin (Box 105)
      - Christoffersen, Jean (Box 105)
      - Claiborne, Robert R. (Box 105)
      - Clark, David Lang (Box 105)
      - Clark, John W. (Box 105)
      - Clark, Richard N. (Box 105)
      - Clarkson, David H. (Box 105)
      - Clayborne, Roscoe (Box 105)
      - Cochran, David Rea (Box 105)
      - Coffee, Jonathon Bachman, Jr. (Box 105)
      - Colburn, John Charles (Box 105)
      - Cole, Aziel Dow (Box 105)
      - Cole, George W. (Box 105)
      - Coleman, John (Box 105)
      - Colton, Joseph Scudder (Box 105)
      - Cone, Leslie W. (Box 105)
      - Connell, Howard Bruce (Box 105)
      - Conover, James Francis (Box 105)
      - Cook, Herbert J. (Box 105)
      - Coolbaugh, Frank C. (Box 105)
      - Coolidge, John K. (Box 105)
      - Cooper, Richard (Box 105)
      - Corbett, Sidney (Box 105)
      - Corson, Levi H. (Box 105)
      - Cottrell, John L. (Box 105)
      - Courteau, Arthur George Thomas (Box 105)
      - Craig, W. Gordon (Box 105)
      - Crane, Samuel R. (Box 105)
      - Creighton, Susan (Box 105)
      - Culleney, George W. (Box 105)
      - Cuming, Francis H. (Box 105)
      - Cunningham, Robert Wilson (Box 105)
      - Curran, David Wellington (Box 105)
      - Curtis, James Wallace (Box 105)
      - Curzon, Donald J. (Box 105)
      - Cushman, Marcus K. (Box 105)
      - Cuthbert, Thomas Hinds (Box 105)
      - Damer, Martin (Box 105)
      - Datson, William J. (Box 105)
      - David, John S. (Box 105)
      - Davidson, J. Lavere (Box 105)
      - Daviou, Albert G. (Box 105)
      - Davis, Edgar Foster (Box 105)
      - Davis, Gordon Davis (Box 105)
      - Davis, James Wendel (Box 105)
      - Dawson, William Vincent (Box 105)
      - Deacon, Percy Robert (Box 105)
      - DeCoux, Charles John (Box 105)
      - Deis, Frederick G. (Box 105)
      - DeMerchant, Barton Wilson [Kountze?] (Box 105)
      - DeMerchant, Louise Kountze (Box 105)
      - Dennis, Richard H. (Box 105)
      - DeRosset, Frederick A. (Box 105)
      - Dibble, Charles Ralph (Box 105)
      - Dickinson, Thomas (Box 105)
      - Dixon, Don Marshall (Box 105)
      - Doan, Edward Slade (Box 105)
      - Dodd, William Porter, Jr. (Box 105)
      - Dodshon, Joseph H. (Box 105)
      - Doherty, Richard Bransby (Box 105)
      - Dollahite, Damian Gene (Box 105)
      - Donohue, Charles (Box 105)
      - Dooley, Thomas B. (Box 105)
      - Dorrien, Gary (Box 105)
      - Douglas, Dufferin D. (Box 105)
      - Dowdell, Victor Lyle (Box 105)
      - Draeger, Walter Raymond, Jr. (Box 105)
      - Drew, Frederick J. (Box 105)
      - Drewe, George H. (Box 105)
      - DuDomaine, Alfred Louis (Box 105)
      - Duff, Edward M. (Box 105)
      - DuMoulin, W. H. (Box 105)
      - Dunkerley, Knight William (Box 105)
      - Dunlop, Walter Stephens (Box 105)
      - Dunn, Don D. (Box 105)
      - Dunn, John K. (Box 105)
      - Dunn, Robert William (Box 105)
      - Dymond, Ernest G. (Box 105)
      - Earp, Samuel (Box 105)
      - Eastman, George C. V. (Box 105)
      - Eickwort, Kathleen R. (Box 105)
      - Eller, Francis Arthur Thorold (Box 105)
      - Ellis, Everett Francis (Box 105)
      - Emenheiser, David Edward (Box 105)
      - Emery, Richard Arlean (Box 105)
      - Engle, George B. (Box 105)
      - Engle, Mark Christopher (Box 105)
      - English, John Lyle (Box 105)
      - Erwin, William Portwood (Box 105)
      - Ethridge, Samuel S. (Box 105)
      - Evans, John Douglas (Box 105)
      - Evatt, Robert Bayley (Box 105)
      - Evett, Douglas Paul (Box 105)
      - Ewens, John George (Box 105)
      - Ewert, Albert Merritt (Box 105)
      - (F-L) (Box 105)
        (files not received)
      - Macfarlane, Peter (Box 105)
      - Madeley, Joseph George (Box 105)
      - Magee, Edward (Box 105)
      - Magrath, John T. (Box 105)
      - Malottke, William N. (Box 105)
      - Man, Robert M. (Box 105)
      - Mangrum, John Fuller (Box 105)
      - Mann, Austin W. (Box 105)
      - Marsh, Karl E. (Box 105)
      - Martin, Marcus Henry (Box 105)
      - Martin, Robert A. (Box 105)
      - Martin, W. H. (Box 105)
      - Mason, Richard (Box 105)
      - Matrau, B. F. (Box 105)
      - Matthias, William (Box 105)
      - McCabe III, Charles (Box 105)
      - McCandless, George J. (Box 105)
      - McCarty, John D. (Box 105)
      - McClenahan, Helen (Box 105)
      - McClone, James A. (Box 105)
      - McClory, Henry (Box 105)
      - McCormick, John Brian (Box 106)
      - McCormick, John Newton (Box 106)
      - McCoskry, Samuel Allen (Box 106)
      - McCoy, Isaac (Box 106)
      - McDougall, Robert F. (Box 106)
      - McFarlane, Mr. (Box 106)
      - McGrath, John T. (Box 106)
      - McIlvaino, Charles Pettit (Box 106)
      - McKay, M. Putnam (Box 106)
      - McKenzie, John Heywood (Box 106)
      - McMurdy, Robert (Box 106)
      - McNeil, Dudley B. (Box 106)
      - McNulty, J. Archibald (Box 106)
      - McPheeter, John William Jr. (Box 106)
      - Mead, James B. (Box 106)
      - Meeks, Howard Samuel (Box 106)
      - Mendenhall, Cyrus (Box 106)
      - Merrill, Edwin W. (Box 106)
      - Meyers, Ruth (Box 106)
      - Mezacapa, Nicklas A. (Box 106)
      - Miller, Pamela (Box 106)
      - Miller, Sherman (Box 106)
      - Milnes, Mary A. (Box 106)
      - Mitchell, Albert Robert (Box 106)
      - Mitchell, R. James (Box 106)
      - Moffat, Walter (Box 106)
      - Moffett, William H. (Box 106)
      - Moore, Everett Alfred (Box 106)
      - Moore, G.S.A. (Box 106)
      - Moran, Samuel Wilson (Box 106)
      - Morford, Kenneth A. (Box 106)
      - Morgan, Austen F. (Box 106)
      - Morrall, William (Box 106)
      - Morrill, Clinton L. (Box 106)
      - Morris, Moseley (Box 106)
      - Morrison, Samuel Warfield (Box 106)
      - Mortimer, George D. E. (Box 106)
      - Morton, J. J. (Box 106)
      - Mosher, Philip W. (Box 106)
      - Mowry, Harris Jenkins, Jr. (Box 106)
      - Munday, Winfred Alban (Box 106)
      - Murphy, William M. (Box 106)
      - Murray, A. L. (Box 106)
      - Myers, Fredrick Eugene (Box 106)
      - Naidoo, Henry (Box 106)
      - Nancarrow, Philip J. (Box 106)
      - Nash, E. G. (Box 106)
      - Nash, R. S. (Box 106)
      - Nattermann, Margaret Ann (Box 106)
      - Neale, Don, Jr. (Box 106)
      - Neckerman, Ernest (Box 106)
      - Neighbors, Maria (Box 106)
      - Neill, Margaret (Box 106)
      - Neilson, Rev. Kurt (Box 106)
      - Neiman, Joseph Clayton (Box 106)
      - Neiman, Judi (Box 106)
      - Nelson, Herman F. (Box 106)
      - Nelson, Luke (Box 106)
      - Neuhaus, Theodore (Box 106)
      - Newell, Tige (Box 106)
      - Newton, Oliver E. (Box 106)
      - Nicholson, Harry L. (Box 106)
      - Nieman, John S. (Box 106)
      - Noble, John (Box 106)
      - Noble, Louis LeGrand (Box 106)
      - Nock, Edwin G. (Box 106)
      - North, Robert D. (Box 106)
      - North, Robert David (Box 106)
      - Northcraft, Linda (Box 106)
      - Nutter, James W. (Box 106)
      - O'Brien, William (Box 106)
      - O'Leary, William (Box 106)
      - O'Meara, Frederick C. (Box 106)
      - Oakes, Rev. Louise K. (Box 106)
      - Oberheide, Richard Dean (Box 106)
      - Odekirk, Dennis R. (Box 106)
      - Okkerse, Kenneth H. (Box 106)
      - Olmeda-Jacquenod, Nina (Box 106)
      - Olmstead, Wayne Carr (Box 106)
      - Oppen, Carl E. G. (Box 106)
      - Ordway, Dustin P. (Box 106)
      - Osberger, Charles (Box 106)
      - Osborne, William H. (Box 106)
      - Ostensen, Roy (Box 106)
      - Ott, Jane (Box 106)
      - Overby, Alexander (Box 106)
      - Packard, Linda A. (Box 106)
      - Paddock, Bishop (Box 106)
      - Paine, Robert (Box 106)
      - Palmer, Edmond B. (Box 106)
      - Paran, Bill (Box 106)
      - Paran, William (Box 106)
      - Pardee, Luther (Box 106)
      - Parini, Barbara (Box 106)
      - Parker, James (Box 106)
      - Parker, Thomas LeRoy (Box 106)
      - Parkhurst, Lawrence M. (Box 106)
      - Parkinson, Herbert H. (Box 106)
      - Parson, John Henry (Box 106)
      - Pasco, Wendell Manning (Box 106)
      - Patronik, Joseph A. (Box 106)
      - Patston, John Ralph (Box 106)
      - Patterson, Frederick A. (Box 106)
      - Patton, David Cecil (Box 106)
      - Paul, Stephen H. (Box 106)
      - Paulsen, Mark G. (Box 106)
      - Payson, Charles B. (Box 106)
      - Peacock, Virginia (Box 106)
      - Pearse, Max Milton, Jr. (Box 106)
      - Pearson, Alonzo (Box 106)
      - Peatross, L. A. (Box 106)
      - Pellett, Harold Austin (Box 106)
      - Pennington, Jasper (Box 106)
      - Perkins, Harry W. (Box 106)
      - Perry, Bonnie (Box 106)
      - Perry, Lawrence (Box 106)
      - Perschbacher, Harold John (Box 106)
      - Perschbacher, Wesley Adolph (Box 106)
      - Peters, Gerret E. (Box 106)
      - Peters, Roger Hansen (Box 106)
      - Peterson, John C. R. (Box 106)
      - Peterson, John L. (Box 106)
      - Petrie, William J. (Box 106)
      - Phares, Max V. (Box 106)
      - Phelps, Joseph (Box 106)
      - Philips, Kathy (Box 106)
      - Philipson, Ernest Edward McDowell (Box 106)
      - Phillips, Frederick Phillips (Box 106)
      - Phillips, Joseph F. (Box 106)
      - Phillips, Michael (Box 106)
      - Pike, Clifford (Box 106)
      - Pike, David R. (Box 106)
      - Pink, Harry Leigh (Box 106)
      - Pipes, Edw. Jerome (Box 106)
      - Pollard, William G. (Box 106)
      - Porter, John (Box 106)
      - Postel, James Looft (Box 106)
      - Potter, Leslie F. (Box 106)
      - Potts, David M. (Box 106)
      - Poulos, John (Box 106)
      - Powell, Anna (Box 106)
      - Powell, Blanche (Box 106)
      - Poyser, Willis William Henry (Box 106)
      - Prechtel, Daniel Lyon (Box 106)
      - Pressey, Stephen (Box 106)
      - Prichard, Joseph Burton (Box 106)
      - Prince, Christopher (Box 106)
      - Pritchard, Joseph P. (Box 106)
      - Pruce, William M. (Box 106)
      - Pulford, Samuel D. (Box 106)
      - Purdue, Henry (Box 106)
      - Rademaker, Robert L. (Box 106)
      - Raeger, Thomas (Box 106)
      - Raih, Donald (Box 106)
      - Randall, Henry C. (Box 106)
      - Ray, John Wainwright (Box 106)
      - Ray, Thomas Kreider (Box 106)
      - Raymond, John Tanner (Box 106)
      - Reed, F. P. O. (Box 106)
      - Reed, William Wellington (Box 106)
      - Reeves, Abraham (Box 106)
      - Reeves, Skip (Box 106)
      - Reeves, William T., Jr. (Box 106)
      - Reid, Sue (Box 106)
      - Reimer, Clarence C. (Box 107)
      - Reishus, John William (Box 107)
      - Reynolds, Joe Douglas (Box 107)
      - Rice, Kenneth Ives (Box 107)
      - Rice, Norman Stanley (Box 107)
      - Rich, III, Edward R. (Box 107)
      - Richards, Leonard B. (Box 107)
      - Richardson, William Price, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Rippey, John Newton (Box 107)
      - Ritter, Charles (Box 107)
      - Roberts, Frederick Constable (Box 107)
      - Roberts, H. M. (Box 107)
      - Roberts, Ray Everett Roberts, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Rogers, Alexander H. (Box 107)
      - Rogers, Lewis C. (Box 107)
      - Rogers, Lewis L. (Box 107)
      - Rollins, John (Box 107)
      - Rollins, Roger Burton (Box 107)
      - Roos, Carl (Box 107)
      - Roosevelt, Sherwood (Box 107)
      - Rose, Doane E. (Box 107)
      - Rose, L. A. S. R. (Box 107)
      - Ross, Harry Stewart Spencer (Box 107)
      - Ross, Merton Winfred (Box 107)
      - Roudenbush, Frank (Box 107)
      - Rowe, Gary (Box 107)
      - Russell, Francis T. (Box 107)
      - Russell, John (Box 107)
      - Russell, R. Allan (Box 107)
      - Safford, Henry (Box 107)
      - Samuel, Jason (Box 107)
      - Sargent, George Paul Torrence (Box 107)
      - Sauls, Stacy (Box 107)
      - Schaffer, John (Box 107)
      - Schaffer, John (Box 107)
      - Schetky, George Paterson (Box 107)
      - Schiesler, Bob (Box 107)
      - Schlotterbeck, Ian Josef (Box 107)
      - Schmitz, Barbara (Box 107)
      - Schueddig, Louis Charles, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Schuneman, Steven L. (Box 107)
      - Schuneman, Steven Lawrence (Box 107)
      - Schuyler, Montgomery (Box 107)
      - Schwert, Douglas Peter (Box 107)
      - Scott, Roger T. (Box 107)
      - Scott, Walter (Box 107)
      - Scribner, Jean (Box 107)
      - Scully, Edward Anthony (Box 107)
      - Seabrook, Alex (Box 107)
      - Seabrook, John Allan (Box 107)
      - Sedgwick, R. Stephen (Box 107)
      - Seeley, Burns Kellar (Box 107)
      - Selkrig, James (Box 107)
      - Semon, Kenneth Jeffery (Box 107)
      - Semon-Scott, Deborah (Box 107)
      - Seymour, Edward (Box 107)
      - Seymour, Gary R. (Box 107)
      - Seymour, Ira P. (Box 107)
      - Seymour, Pat (Box 107)
      - Shackelford, Rev. (Box 107)
      - Shaefer, Harry (Box 107)
      - Shahan, Robert R. (Box 107)
      - Shakles, Robert Andrew (Box 107)
      - Shambaugh, Benjamin A. (Box 107)
      - Sharp, James Raymond (Box 107)
      - Shaver, John (Box 107)
      - Shaver, Thomas R. (Box 107)
      - Shearer, Donald (Box 107)
      - Sheldon, Peggy Ann (Box 107)
      - Shepard, Irving Valentine (Box 107)
      - Shepard, John (Box 107)
      - Sherfick, Kenneth Lyle (Box 107)
      - Shoub, Donald A. (Box 107)
      - Shoulders, David (Box 107)
      - Shumaker, John (Box 107)
      - Simmons, Gregory (Box 107)
      - Simms, William A. (Box 107)
      - Simons, David Warren (Box 107)
      - Sims, Gregory Brian (Box 107)
      - Sirotko, Theodore Francis (Box 107)
      - Skillicorn, Gerald Amos (Box 107)
      - Skinner, G. M. (Box 107)
      - Skinner, James Donald (Box 107)
      - Skinner, Nelson Bogart (Box 107)
      - Slack, James (Box 107)
      - Slade, A. Worger (Box 107)
      - Sloan III, Carey E. (Box 107)
      - Smileau, Franklin C. (Box 107)
      - Smith, Allyne Levoit, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Smith, Ann-Lining (Box 107)
      - Smith, Barbara J. (Box 107)
      - Smith, Franklin Campbell (Box 107)
      - Smith, George Wayne (Box 107)
      - Smith, Gordon V. (Box 107)
      - Smith, Murdock (Box 107)
      - Smith, Phineas (Box 107)
      - Smith, Robert Angus (Box 107)
      - Smith, Roger William (Box 107)
      - Smith, Thomas, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Smith-Kurtz, Mary Bonnagean "Bonnie" (Box 107)
      - Smythe, W. Herbert (Box 107)
      - Snoxell, W. Eugene (Box 107)
      - Snyder, Albert W. (Box 107)
      - Solem, Henry R. (Box 107)
      - Somerville, Henry E. S. (Box 107)
      - Sowerby, Herbert (Box 107)
      - Spaid, William (Box 107)
      - Spann, Hugh Randall (Box 107)
      - Sparling, William Heavener (Box 107)
      - Spatches, Montraville E. (Box 107)
      - Spaulding, Voltaire (Box 107)
      - Spitler, Thomas L. (Box 107)
      - St. Amour III, Frank (Box 107)
      - St. Andrew, Ernest R. (Box 107)
      - St. Johns, Ernest Keyes (Box 107)
      - Stam, George Allen (Box 107)
      - Stanley, John Hiram, Jr. (Box 107)
      - Stanley, M. C. (Box 107)
      - Stearns, Chilton Rupert (Box 107)
      - Stearns, Joanne (Box 107)
      - Stephens, Steinman E. (Box 107)
      - Stevens, Fred Harding (Box 107)
      - Stevenson, Robert Lapsley (Box 107)
      - Stoll, Thomas Fothergill (Box 107)
      - Stonex, William G. (Box 107)
      - Stoppel, Gerald Corwin (Box 107)
      - Story, Mark Denslow (Box 107)
      - Stout, Charles T. (Box 107)
      - Stowe, William (Box 107)
      - Stowell, Philip (Box 107)
      - Stravers, Richard (Box 107)
      - Strey, Robert J. (Box 107)
      - Strey, Robert J. (Box 107)
      - Strickin, Paul (Box 107)
      - Strom, John David (Box 107)
      - Strong, Henry N. (Box 107)
      - Stuart, Charles M. (Box 107)
      - Studwell, William Guion (Box 107)
      - Suriner, Noreen (Box 107)
      - Swanson, Carl D. (Box 107)
      - Sweeney, W. Terry (Box 107)
      - Sweet, Sidney (Box 107)
      - Swickard, Philip (Box 107)
      - Swinton, George Donald (Box 107)
      - Sword, John (Box 107)
      - Talbott, Lucy B. (Box 107)
      - Tan Creti, Michael J. (Box 107)
      - Taylor Weiss, Douglas (Box 107)
      - Taylor, Mary Ann (Box 107)
      - Thompson, Charles (Box 107)
      - Thornburg, Michael (Box 107)
      - Thweatt, Richmond F. III (Box 107)
      - Tirman, Tom (Box 107)
      - Townsend, Jerrald (Box 107)
      - Travis, Carrol (Box 107)
      - Whittemore, Lewis (Box 107)
- Standing Committee Files
  The Standing Committee series contains papers that span the period 1936 to 1955. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - Papers, 1936; 1942-1955
    - Papers, 1936; 1942-1949; 11 folders (Box 55)
    - 1950-1955, 8 folders (Box 56)
- Miscellaneous Files
  The Miscellaneous Files series contains papers that cover both financial and diocesan matters, as well as contains list of confirmations and clergy members. The series spans the period 1875-1968.
  - Clergy Index (Box 56)
  - Confirmation Lists, 1919-1923; 1930-1949; 19 folders (Box 56)
  - Financial Reports, 1932; 1949-1952; 3 folders (Box 56)
  - Financial Reports, 1955-1960; 3 folders (Box 56)
  - Bishop George D. Gillespie Vade Mecum, 1882 (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Diocesan Record of Election of Rectors, Appointment of Missionaries, and Notice of Resignations of Parishes and Missionaries, 1875-1890 (Volume 6)
  - Monthly Reports, 1942; 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Notebook concerning trends in parish membership, 1950; 3 volumes (Box 57)
  - "Ordinations, Depositions, and Restorations,", 1939-1956 (Box 57)
  - Parish Reports, 1940-1943; 4 folders (Box 57)
  - Printed Material concerning Akeley Hall, 1920-1921 (Box 57)
  - Printed Material concerning miscellaneous subjects, 1926-1968; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Register of Official Acts, 1913-1917 (Box 57)
  - Survey Report of the Diocese, 1951 (Box 57)
  - Women's Auxiliary, 1924-1937 (Box 57)
- Diocesan Record Books
  The Diocesan Record Books series contains late nineteenth and early twentieth century, books detailing the activities of the individual clergymen in the diocese.
  - Annual Convention Journal, 1880-1893 (Volume 7)
  - Journal of the Diocese of Western Michigan, 1894-1909 (Volume 8)
  - List of Clergy, circa 1875-1908 (Volume 9)
  - List of Ordinations, 1875-circe 1908 (Volume 10)
  - List of Visitations, 1875-1909 (Volume 11)
- Publicity Files (Elizabeth Slye)
  The Publicity Files contains papers of Elizabeth Slye, arranged alphabetically, and primarily concerned with the diocesan publications. The series spans the period from 1904-1968 with the majority of the papers from the 1960s.
  - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 57)
  - Press Releases, 1962-1968; 5 folders (Box 57)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1965-1967 (Box 57)
  - Papers concerning the history of the guilds at St. Luke's Church in Kalamazoo, 1904-1963 (Box 57)
  - Newsletters from Bishop Bennison to the Clergy, 1963-1965 (Box 57)
  - Papers concerning the Annual Convention of the Diocese, 1963-1968; 6 folders (Box 57)
  - Papers concerning the magazine Living Church, 1965-1967 (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning the Episcopal Churchwomen, 1966 (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning the Convention of the Episcopal Churchwomen, 1962; 1964; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning the projects of the Episcopal Churchwomen of St. Luke's Church in Kalamazoo, 1961-1963; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning press relations expenses, 1962-1966 (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning the Conference of Young Women, 1966-1967; 5 folders (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning Family Life House, 1965-1966 (Box 58)
  - Papers concerning Mrs. Ruth Bigelow, 1965-1967 (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1968; 2 folders (Box 58)
- Defunct Parish and Mission Church Records
  The records of Defunct Parish and Mission Churches provide historical and genealogical information dating back to the 1860s for many western Michigan communities.
  - Baldwin (St. Matthew's Mission), Parish Register, 1909-1910 (Box 58)
  - Belding, Holy Trinity Church Register, 1907-1919 (Box 58)
  - Clare (Chapel of St. Ann), Parish Register, 1953-1961; 2 volumes (Box 58)
  - Grand Rapids. Chapel of the Good Shepherd parish register, 1904-1912 (Volume 12)
  - Grand Rapids. St. John's parish register, 1893-1907 (Volume 13)
  - Grand Rapids. Chapel of the Good Shepherd
    - Parish Register, 1871-1901 (Box 59)
    - Record of Services, 1884-1905 (Box 59)
  - Grand Rapids. St. John's minute book, 1894-1903 (Box 59)
  - Grand Rapids. St. Mark's, Girls Friendly Society minute book, 1882-1892 (Box 59)
  - Hastings, Diary of Rev. William C. White, 1897-1921; 7 volumes (Box 59)
  - Ionia (St. John's), Vestry and Parish Meetings, Minutes, 1923-1931 (Box 59)
  - Lee Township (St. Michael and All Angels), Record of Services, 1942-1959; 2 volumes (Box 59)
  - Mendon
    - St. Paul's
      - Parish Register, 1866-1954 (Box 60)
      - Minute Book, 1866-1907 (Box 60)
      - Record of Services, 1940-1945 (Box 60)
    - St. Paul's Guild
      - Minute Book, 1895-1915; 4 volumes (Box 60)
      - Treasurer's Record Book, 1895-1911 (Box 60)
  - Paw Paw (St. Mark's), Parish Register, 1875-1882 (Box 60)
  - South Haven (Church of the Epiphany), Record of Services, 1906-1939 (Box 60)
  - Van Buren County, Register of Mission Stations, 1879-1882 (Box 60)
  - Unknown Parish, Record of Services, 1851-1867 (Box 60)
  - Parish Register (mostly Tustin), 1871-1890 (Volume 14)
- Diocesan Committee Files
  The Diocesan Committee Files series contains the minutes of the Executive Council, the Executive Committee, the Standing Committee and the Finance Committees from 1874 to 1984. Some of these materials will also be found in the Topical Files of the Bishop's Files series
  - Executive Council, Minutes, 1920-1966; 11 volumes (Box 61)
  - Executive Council, Minutes, 1967-1974; 4 volumes (Box 62)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1948-1984 (Box 62)
  - Standing Committee, Minutes, 1874-1957; 2 volumes (Box 62)